beautifulcalendar.net 2017-11-20

# Beautiful Calendar

Beautiful Calendar and its browser extension provider Beautiful Calendar Extension (herein "The provider") are committed to your privacy. Please read our policies below: 

The provider recognize the need to protect the privacy of the personal information of our users. Users should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the use of that information. 

Please take into consideration that this Privacy Policy and the EULA refer only to the Beautiful Calendar browser extension and that each search engine offered to you as part of the Beautiful Calendar browser extension has its own privacy policy and EULA. 

## No Spyware Policy

The browser extension may send unidentifiable and non-personal data. This data is never stored and is used to maintain the correct operation of the offering. Use of the IP address is made to correctly assign weather and language presentation, Use of components usage determines their correct operation, Use of queries enables and is limited to the correct presentation of shopping component, Use of technical information covering the browser and operating system enables correct functioning of the application, as well as the unique identifier of the browser extension. None of the information is stored or kept on our servers at any time. Information is used immediately as it is gathered to maintain the correct operation of the offering. Information cannot be traced back to the end user. Any information gathered is done on an aggregated basis and in no way can be linked to private information such as private individual name, address, telephone or email, which is never collected or stored. 

## No Adware Policy

The browser extension does not launch pop-up or pop-under advertisement windows or any other type of obtrusive ads. Occasionally users may be presented with advertisements while using the browser extension. We might use an outside ad company to display ads to be shown once you are using your preferred search engine. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Website, cookies received with search results pages may be collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

## Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of Beautiful Calendar if you do so. We use cookies to make it easy to our visitors to download graphics on The provider site. We also use cookies to collect demographic and profile data on an aggregate basis for purposes of delivering content specific to users interests. 

## IP addresses

IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as "traffic data" so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you. We also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. The provider will not use your IP address to attempt to identify your personal information. 

## Removing the browser extension

If you wish to uninstall an extension and to remove it completely from the browser: 

  1. Click the Chrome menu on the browser toolbar.
  2. Click Tools.
  3. Select Extensions.
  4. Click the trash can icon by the extension you'd like to completely remove.
  5. A confirmation dialog appears, click Remove.

## External links

Beautiful Calendar contains links to third-party Websites. Please be aware that we cannot control and are not responsible for the information collection practices of third-party Websites and their EULA & Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review and understand the privacy policies and EULAs of these Websites before providing any information to them. 

## Contacting the provider

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or application, or your dealings with them, you can contact us at  [answers@beautifulcalendar.net](mailto:answers@beautifulcalendar.net)

Effective Date: September 2015
